Hi everybody. I'm John Kuryaku and
welcome back to Deep Focus. This is just
going to be a short little clip uh
because I felt it was important to uh
discuss at least uh in in surface terms
this latest revelation from the Justice
Department on the Jeffrey Epstein case.
First of all, uh, FBI Director Cash
Patel and FBI Deputy Director Dan Bonino
have concluded in no uncertain terms
that Jeffrey Epstein committed suicide.
I have always maintained that Jeffrey
Epstein committed suicide and that's
because of my own experience in the
Federal Bureau of Prisons. First of all,
the BOP is a repository for the biggest
boobs in public service.
You have to understand how stupid these
people are, how incompetent they are.
Oh, people say the cameras weren't
working. Well, news flash, the cameras
never work in prisons.
Anybody who's ever been in prison will
tell you that. Number two, oh, the
guards were asleep. Yeah, at any given
time of the day or night, you go past
the guard booth in prison, the guards
are asleep or they're playing solitire
or they're surfing the internet. Uh,
number three, they put Epstein in with
uh somebody that was supposed to protect
him or watch that he didn't commit
suicide and they put him in with a
killer. Yeah, because like I said,
they're incompetent boobs. So, Dr.
Biden's conclusion aside that it was
more likely a homicide. The video shows
literally nothing. The final conclusion
is that it was a suicide. Okay, I agree
with that.
What I disagree with
is this notion that there are no files,
that there is no dossier, that there is
no black book of clients. I don't
believe that for a second. You know,
we've said a million times the deep
state is real. The deep state exists.
You don't have to call it the deep
state. You can call it the federal
bureaucracy. You can call it the state.
The fact of the matter is presidents
come and go. FBI directors and deputy
directors and attorneys general come and
go. But those civil servants who
actually make the trains run on time are
there forever. It's not unusual for
people to have 30, 35, even 40year
careers in public service. That's what
the deep state is. Now, yesterday on Fox
News, I compared uh this announcement
from the Justice Department with a
similar announcement in 1975 from the
Church Committee, which became the
Senate Select Committee on Intelligence.
The Senate Select Committee int on
intelligence under the the chairmanship
of Senator Frank Church, then a Democrat
from Idaho
ordered the CIA to produce all documents
related to a very ugly program called MK
Ultra. The director of the CIA then went
back to CIA headquarters and ordered
that all the documents be destroyed.
That's illegal,
but good luck proving it. And so what we
know now about MK Ultra is what we have
learned from the 20% of the documents
that survived that illegal order. I
would bet money on the notion that the
same thing has happened with the Jeffrey
Epstein documents. And I'm I'm not
saying that Cash Patel and Dan Bino knew
anything about it, but I think that
there are very powerful forces at work
in that sub level of leadership
at some place like the FBI or the
Department of Justice that wanted to
ensure that this thing doesn't get any
bigger than it already has. And if there
are no documents to prove any
malfeasants on the part of any important
person,
then eventually the thing's going to go
away.
One other point.
They want us to believe that the only
people involved in a major pedophilic
sex trafficking scandal
were Jeffrey Epstein
and Gileain Maxwell.
I have to call on that.
You can't run an international pedophile
sex trafficking ring
with two people from the A-list of uh
society. What about all of the so-called
security uh people that Epstein had who
were monitoring the big banks of of
monitors to to watch the hidden cameras
in every one of those bedrooms and every
one of the bathrooms, too, by the way?
What about those people? Why have
charges never been filed against Prince
Andrew?
Right? He should be charged with crimes
against children. What about any of the
other people who had sex with uh with
minors at Jeffrey Epstein's island?
Virginia was was very very clear about
what happened to her, as were five or
six other young women.
So where are the prosecutions?
As I said, I think the fix is in
I hate to say, but knowing how
government works, I think this thing is
done. We're not going to get any more
information. What we've gotten is going
to be the extent of it. And I think that
both Democrats and Republicans are
hoping right now that this thing just
goes away. Do me a favor and hit the
like and subscribe button. I can't tell
you how much that helps me. It It means
so much to me to be able to build up a
following and we can keep these things
going that way. So, thanks for joining
me and we'll see you next time on Deep
Focus. Bye-bye.